girls20.org 2017-08-31

# Privacy | G(irls)20

G(irls)20 places a high value on privacy, both in person and online. G(irls)20 is committed to maintaining the privacy of all individuals who use [www.girls20summit.com](http://www.girls20summit.com/) and [www.FathersEmpoweringDaughters.org](http://www.fathersempoweringdaughters.org/).

This Site may contain links to other web sites. Upon entering other sites, you are subject to the privacy and security policies of those sites. This policy identifies the privacy practices of the [www.girls20summit.com](http://www.girls20summit.com/) and [www.FathersEmpoweringDaughters.org](http://www.fathersempoweringdaughters.org/) sites only.

This Site uses and collects digital cookies to gather general trend data concerning traffic on the website for statistical analysis. This information is used for auditing and tracking purposes and to improve the content of the Site. The data we collect is used both collectively and individually for website research to create a better experience for the users of this site. This information is not linked with any individual or IP address.

No personal information (which means personally-identifiable information including, without limitation, name, street address, telephone number, screen name and e-mail address) about the user is collected from users of this Site unless specifically and clearly requested, and only when the user provides it voluntarily. It is our policy that personal information of the users of our site is private and confidential. Accordingly, any personal information you provide is stored in a secure location accessible only by designated staff.

We only use personal information provided for the express purpose for which it was collected unless the user specifically agrees to the use of the personal information for additional purposes. Personal information will not be shared with any third party.

As a user of this Site who has provided personal information to us you can have access to your personal information for the purposes of correcting or updating any of your personal information or to delete the personal information you provided on this Site from our records.
